export const chapter = "Chapter -17: Calling up a Friend  ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Who is answering the phone call?",
          optionA: "Rajni",
          optionB: "Swati",
          optionC: "Soma",
          correctAnswer: "Soma",
        },
        {
          question: "What is Soma preparing for next week?",
          optionA: "Vacation",
          optionB: "Birthday party",
          optionC: "School event",
          correctAnswer: "Birthday party",
        },
        {
          question: "What did Rajni give Soma as a gift last year?",
          optionA: "Hair band",
          optionB: "Necklace",
          optionC: "Bracelet",
          correctAnswer: "Hair band",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why does Rajni think Soma didn't like the gift from last year?",
          optionA: "Soma didn't wear it",
          optionB: "Soma lost it",
          optionC: "Soma didn't say thank you",
          correctAnswer: "Soma didn't wear it",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What did Soma's sister, Swati, do with the hair band from last year's gift?",
          optionA: "Wore it to school",
          optionB: "Lost it",
          optionC: "Gave it to Rajni",
          correctAnswer: "Wore it to school",
        },
        {
          question: "What does Soma say about Rajni's choice of colors?",
          optionA: "It needs improvement",
          optionB: "It is terrible",
          optionC: "She is proud of it",
          correctAnswer: "She is proud of it",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When is Soma planning to call Rajni to invite her to the birthday party?",
          optionA: "Tomorrow",
          optionB: "Next week",
          optionC: "Today",
          correctAnswer: "Tomorrow",
        },
        {
          question: "What does Rajni say about coming to the birthday party?",
          optionA: "She won't come",
          optionB: "She will come only if invited",
          optionC: "She will come anyway",
          correctAnswer: "She will come anyway",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What does Soma express towards Rajni at the end of the conversation?",
          optionA: "Anger",
          optionB: "Love",
          optionC: "Indifference",
          correctAnswer: "Love",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What did Rajni give Soma as a gift last year, according to Soma?",
          optionA: "Hair band",
          optionB: "Necklace",
          optionC: "Bracelet",
          correctAnswer: "Hair band",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "______ picks up the receiver.",
          optionA: "Rajni",
          optionB: "Swati",
          optionC: "Soma",
          correctAnswer: "Soma",
        },
        {
          question: "Soma is preparing for ______ next week.",
          optionA: "Vacation",
          optionB: "Birthday party",
          optionC: "School event",
          correctAnswer: "Birthday party",
        },
        {
          question: "Last year, Rajni gave Soma a ______ as a gift.",
          optionA: "Hair band",
          optionB: "Necklace",
          optionC: "Bracelet",
          correctAnswer: "Hair band",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Rajni thinks Soma didn't like the gift because Soma didn't ______ it.",
          optionA: "Wear",
          optionB: "Lose",
          optionC: "Thank",
          correctAnswer: "Wear",
        },
        {
          question: "Soma's sister, Swati, wore the hair band to ______.",
          optionA: "Vacation",
          optionB: "School",
          optionC: "Birthday party",
          correctAnswer: "School",
        },
        {
          question: "Soma is proud of Rajni's choice of ______.",
          optionA: "Colors",
          optionB: "Clothes",
          optionC: "Gifts",
          correctAnswer: "Colors",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Soma is planning to call Rajni to invite her to the ______ party.",
          optionA: "Vacation",
          optionB: "Birthday",
          optionC: "School",
          correctAnswer: "Birthday",
        },
        {
          question: "Rajni will come to the party ______ if invited or not.",
          optionA: "Anyway",
          optionB: "Only",
          optionC: "Never",
          correctAnswer: "Anyway",
        },
        {
          question:
            "At the end of the conversation, Soma expresses ______ towards Rajni.",
          optionA: "Anger",
          optionB: "Love",
          optionC: "Indifference",
          correctAnswer: "Love",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Rajni gave Soma a ______ as a gift last year, according to Soma.",
          optionA: "Hair band",
          optionB: "Necklace",
          optionC: "Bracelet",
          correctAnswer: "Hair band",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Soma is preparing for a vacation next week.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Rajni gave Soma a necklace as a gift last year.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Soma's sister, Swati, lost the hair band given by Rajni.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Rajni believes Soma didn't like the gift because she didn't say thank you.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Soma is proud of Rajni's choice of clothes.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Rajni will come to the birthday party only if invited.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "At the end of the conversation, Soma expresses anger towards Rajni.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Rajni gave Soma a hair band as a gift last year, and Soma wore it many times.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Soma is planning to call Rajni to invite her to a school event.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Rajni suggests that the man who imprisoned them in the zoo is wise.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
